Tracy Early papers, Inclusive: 1924-2005, Bulk: circa 1940-2005
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Magazine and Newspaper Articles, 1947-2005; 1
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (6 of 10), 1992, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (7 of 10), 1993 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (8 of 10), 1993, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (9 of 10), 1994 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Ecumenical Press Service: (10 of 10), 1994 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Ambassador Life, 1947 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - American Bible Society, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - A.D.: (1 of 12), 1972-1973 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - A.D.: (2 of 12), 1976-1977 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - A.D.: (3 of 12), 1977 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - A.D.: (4 of 12), 1977 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - A.D.: (6 of 12), 1978 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - A.D.: (7 of 12), 1979 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - A.D.: (8 of 12), 1981 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - A.D.: (9 of 12), 1982 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - A.D.: (10 of 12), 1982 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - A.D.: (11 of 12), 1982 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - A.D.: (12 of 12), 1982 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Ave. Maria, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Baptist Press, 1974, 1976, 1989 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Baptist Program: (1 of 3), 1966 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Baptist Program: (2 of 3), 1966-1967 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Baptist Program: (3 of 3), 1967 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Catholic New York, 1984-1986, 1989-1990, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - The Catholic Observer, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - The Christian Century: (1 of 6), 1971-1972, 1974-1975, 1978, 1980, 1982, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - The Christian Century: (2 of 6), 1970-1972 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - The Christian Century: (3 of 6), 1969-1970 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - The Christian Century: (4 of 6), 1969-1970 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - The Christian Century: (5 of 6), 1969 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - The Christian Century: (6 of 6), 1967-1972 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - The Christian Century: (1 of 4), 1969-1970, 1972, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - The Christian Century: (2 of 4), 1971 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - The Christian Century: (3 of 4), 1970-1972 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - The Christian Century: (4 of 4), 1972 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - The Christian Herald: (1 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - The Christian Herald: (2 of 3), 1976 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - The Christian Herald: (3 of 3), 1976 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - The Christian Herald: (1 of 7), 1975-1976 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - The Christian Herald: (2 of 7), 1976 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - The Christian Herald: (3 of 7), 1967, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - The Christian Herald: (4 of 7), 1970 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - The Christian Herald: (5 of 7), 1971-1972 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - The Christian Herald: (6 of 7), 1971-1973 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - The Christian Herald: (7 of 7), 1973 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - The Christian Herald: (1 of 5), 1973 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - The Christian Herald: (2 of 5), 1974 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - The Christian Herald: (3 of 5), 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - The Christian Herald: (4 of 5), 1975 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - The Christian Herald: (5 of 5), 1975 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - The Christian Herald: (1 of 5), 1975-1977, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - The Christian Herald: (2 of 5), 1977 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - The Christian Herald: (3 of 5), 1977 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - The Christian Herald: (4 of 5), 1978-1979 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - The Christian Herald: (5 of 5), 1978-1980 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Christianity Today, 1959 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Church & Society, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Colleague: (1 of 3), 1980 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Colleague: (2 of 3), 1979-1980 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Colleague: (3 of 3), 1980 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Colliers, 1970, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Custom Book, 1982, undated (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Editorial Department: (1 of 4), 1983 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Editorial Department: (2 of 4), 1983-1984 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Editorial Department: (3 of 4), 1984 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Editorial Department: (4 of 4), 1984, undated (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Editorial Department: (1 of 3), 1985 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Editorial Department: (2 of 3), 1985 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Editorial Department: (3 of 3), 1990, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Ecumenical News International: (1 of 16), 1994 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Ecumenical News International: (2 of 16), 1994 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Ecumenical News International: (3 of 16), 1994 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Ecumenical News International: (4 of 16), 1994-1995 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Ecumenical News International: (5 of 16), 1995 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Ecumenical News International: (6 of 16), 1995 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Ecumenical News International: (7 of 16), 1995-1996 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Ecumenical News International: (8 of 16), 1996 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Ecumenical News International: (9 of 16), 1996 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Ecumenical News International: (10 of 16), 1996 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Ecumenical News International: (11 of 16), 1996 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Ecumenical News International: (12 of 16), 1996 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Ecumenical News International: (13 of 16), 1996 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Ecumenical News International: (14 of 16), 1996 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Ecumenical News International: (15 of 16), 1996 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Ecumenical News International: (16 of 16), 1996 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Ecumenical News International: (1 of 10), 1997 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Ecumenical News International: (2 of 10), 1997 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Ecumenical News International: (3 of 10), 1997 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Ecumenical News International: (4 of 10), 1997 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Ecumenical News International: (5 of 10), 1997 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Ecumenical News International: (6 of 10), 1997 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Ecumenical News International: (7 of 10), 1997 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Ecumenical News International: (8 of 10), 1997 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Ecumenical News International: (9 of 10), 1997 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Ecumenical News International: (10 of 10), 1997 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Ecumenical News International: (1 of 2), 1998 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Ecumenical News International: (2 of 2), 1998 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Protestant Episcopal Church in the United States of America: (1 of 5), 1991, 1993, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Protestant Episcopal Church in the United States of America: (2 of 5), 1993 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Protestant Episcopal Church in the United States of America: (3 of 5), 1993-1994 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Protestant Episcopal Church in the United States of America: (4 of 5), 1994, 1996, 1998 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Protestant Episcopal Church in the United States of America: (5 of 5), 1995-1996 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - B’nai B’rith, 1978, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Foreign Features, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Grit: (1 of 3), 1978-1982 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Grit: (2 of 3), 1978 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Grit: (3 of 3), 1971, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Independent News Alliance, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - The Interpreter: (1 of 6), 1980, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - The Interpreter: (2 of 6), 1908, 1980-1982 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - The Interpreter: (3 of 6), 1978-1979, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - The Interpreter: (4 of 6), 1977 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - The Interpreter: (5 of 6), 1977 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - The Interpreter: (6 of 6), 1970, 1977-1978 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Interpretive Services: (1 of 8), 1970, 1972 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Interpretive Services: (2 of 8), 1971-1972 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Interpretive Services: (3 of 8), 1972-1975 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Interpretive Services: (4 of 8), 1973 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Interpretive Services: (5 of 8), 1973-1974 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Interpretive Services: (6 of 8), 1975 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Interpretive Services: (7 of 8), 1975 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Interpretive Services: (8 of 8), 1975 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Interpretive Services: (1 of 5), 1973, 1977-1978 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Interpretive Services: (2 of 5), 1978 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Interpretive Services: (3 of 5), 1978 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Interpretive Services: (4 of 5), 1978 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Interpretive Services: (5 of 5), 1976 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Interpretive Services: (1 of 9), 1980 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Interpretive Services: (2 of 9), 1980 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Interpretive Services: (3 of 9), 1976-1977, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Interpretive Services: (4 of 9), 1977 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Interpretive Services: (5 of 9), 1976-1977 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Interpretive Services: (6 of 9), 1977 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Interpretive Services: (7 of 9), 1977, 1980-1981 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Interpretive Services: (8 of 9), 1981 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Interpretive Services: (9 of 9), 1981 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Jewish Week: (1 of 9), 1986 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Jewish Week: (2 of 9), 1986-1987 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Jewish Week: (3 of 9), 1987 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Jewish Week: (4 of 9), 1987 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Jewish Week: (5 of 9), 1987 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Jewish Week: (6 of 9), 1987-1988 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Jewish Week: (7 of 9), 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Jewish Week: (8 of 9), 1989 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Jewish Week: (9 of 9), 1990-1991 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - United Church of Christ: (1 of 3), 1988 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - United Church of Christ: (2 of 3), 1988 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - United Church of Christ: (3 of 3), 1988 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - LaFarge: (1 of 5), 1984 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - LaFarge: (2 of 5), 1984-1985 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - LaFarge: (3 of 5), 1985 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - LaFarge: (4 of 5), 1985 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - LaFarge: (5 of 5), 1985 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Lamp: (1 of 7), 1968 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Lamp: (2 of 7), 1967-1968 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Lamp: (3 of 7), 1968-1970 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Lamp: (4 of 7), 1969 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Lamp: (5 of 7), 1971 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Lamp: (6 of 7), 1971-1972 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Lamp: (7 of 7), 1969, 1973-1974 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Lutheran Council in the USA: (1 of 8), 1977-1978, 1980-1981 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Lutheran Council in the USA: (2 of 8), 1978, 1980-1981 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Lutheran Council in the USA: (3 of 8), 1979-1981 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Lutheran Council in the USA: (4 of 8), 1981 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Lutheran Council in the USA: (5 of 8), 1981 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Lutheran Council in the USA: (6 of 8), 1981-1982 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Lutheran Council in the USA: (7 of 8), 1982 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Lutheran Council in the USA: (8 of 8), 1981-1982 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Liberty, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Lutheran: (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Lutheran: (2 of 2), 1978-1979 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - National Catholic Reporter: (1 of 3), 1970, 1976, 1978-1979, 1982, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - National Catholic Reporter: (2 of 3), 1978-1979 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - National Catholic Reporter: (3 of 3), 1976, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - National Council of Churches: (1 of 5), 1972-1973 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - National Council of Churches: (2 of 5), 1978, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - National Council of Churches: (3 of 5), 1981, 1983-1984 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - National Council of Churches: (4 of 5), 1985-1987, 1992-1993, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - National Council of Churches: (5 of 5), 1996, 1998-2000, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - New Catholic Encyclopedia: (1 of 7), 1974-1976, 1978, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - New Catholic Encyclopedia: (2 of 7), 1974 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - New Catholic Encyclopedia: (3 of 7), 1974 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - New Catholic Encyclopedia: (4 of 7), 1974 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - New Catholic Encyclopedia: (5 of 7), 1973 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - New Catholic Encyclopedia: (6 of 7), 1971, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - New Catholic Encyclopedia: (7 of 7), 1973 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - New Horizons, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - New Republic, 1974, 1976 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - News Front: (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - News Front: (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - New World Outlook: (1 of 6), 1971 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - New World Outlook: (2 of 6), 1973-1974, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - New World Outlook: (3 of 6), 1973 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - New World Outlook: (4 of 6), 1974 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - New World Outlook: (5 of 6), 1974 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - New World Outlook: (6 of 6), 1973-1974, undated (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - New World Outlook: (1 of 6), 1975 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - New World Outlook: (2 of 6), 1975 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - New World Outlook: (3 of 6), 1975-1976 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - New World Outlook: (4 of 6), 1975 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - New World Outlook: (5 of 6), 1976 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - New World Outlook: (6 of 6), 1976 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - New World Outlook: (1 of 5), 1977 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - New World Outlook: (2 of 5), 1978 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - New World Outlook: (3 of 5), 1978 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - New World Outlook: (4 of 5), 1978 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - New World Outlook: (5 of 5), 1978 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - New World Outlook: (1 of 3), 1978-1979 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - New World Outlook: (2 of 3), 1979-1980 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - New World Outlook: (3 of 3), 1980 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - New World Outlook: (1 of 4), 1981 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - New World Outlook: (2 of 4), 1981 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - New World Outlook: (3 of 4), 1981 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - New World Outlook: (4 of 4), 1981 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - New World Outlook: (1 of 5), 1981-1982 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - New World Outlook: (2 of 5), 1982 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - New World Outlook: (3 of 5), 1982 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - New World Outlook: (4 of 5), 1981-1982 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - New World Outlook: (5 of 5), 1982 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - New World Outlook: (1 of 5), 1983 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - New World Outlook: (2 of 5), 1981-1983 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - New World Outlook: (3 of 5), 1982-1983 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - New World Outlook: (4 of 5), 1983 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - New World Outlook: (5 of 5), 1981-1983 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - New World Outlook: (1 of 7), 1980, 1982, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - New World Outlook: (2 of 7), 1984 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - New World Outlook: (3 of 7), 1984-1985 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - New World Outlook: (4 of 7), 1984-1985 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - New World Outlook: (5 of 7), 1985 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - New World Outlook: (6 of 7), 1985-1986 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - New World Outlook: (7 of 7), 1986 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - New World Outlook: (1 of 5), 1987-1988 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - New World Outlook: (2 of 5), 1988 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - New World Outlook: (3 of 5), 1988 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - New World Outlook: (4 of 5), 1991-1993 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - New World Outlook: (5 of 5), 1994, 1996, 2000-2001 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - One World: (1 of 12), 1994-1995 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - One World: (2 of 12), 1993-1994 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - One World: (3 of 12), 1993 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - One World: (4 of 12), 1990-1991 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - One World: (5 of 12), 1990 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - One World: (6 of 12), 1989-1990 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - One World: (7 of 12), 1988-1989 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - One World: (8 of 12), 1988 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - One World: (9 of 12), 1986-1987 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - One World: (10 of 12), 1983, 1985 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - One World: (11 of 12), 1979-1980 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - One World: (12 of 12), 1978, 1982 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Outlook, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Presbyterian Survey, 1984-1985 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - National Catholic Register: (1 of 2), 1997 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - National Catholic Register: (2 of 2), 1997 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Religious Herald: (1 of 3), 1966-1968, 1982 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Religious Herald: (2 of 3), 1966 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Religious Herald: (3 of 3), 1966-1968 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Religious News Service: (1 of 5), 1966-1968, 1982 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Religious News Service: (2 of 5), 1968-1969 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Religious News Service: (3 of 5), 1969 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Religious News Service: (4 of 5), 1969-1970 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Religious News Service: (5 of 5), 1970 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Religious News Service: (1 of 7), 1968-1970 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Religious News Service: (2 of 7), 1970 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Religious News Service: (3 of 7), 1970 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Religious News Service: (4 of 7), 1970 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Religious News Service: (5 of 7), 1970 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Religious News Service: (6 of 7), 1970 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Religious News Service: (7 of 7), 1970 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Religious News Service: (1 of 9), 1971 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Religious News Service: (2 of 9), 1971 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Religious News Service: (3 of 9), 1971 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Religious News Service: (4 of 9), 1971 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Religious News Service: (5 of 9), 1971 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Religious News Service: (6 of 9), 1971 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Religious News Service: (7 of 9), 1971 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Religious News Service: (8 of 9), 1971 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Religious News Service: (9 of 9), 1971 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Religious News Service: (1 of 7), 1972 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Religious News Service: (2 of 7), 1972 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Religious News Service: (3 of 7), 1972 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Religious News Service: (4 of 7), 1972 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Religious News Service: (5 of 7), 1972 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Religious News Service: (6 of 7), 1972 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Religious News Service: (7 of 7), 1972 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Religious News Service: (1 of 10), 1973 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Religious News Service: (2 of 10), 1973 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Religious News Service: (3 of 10), 1973 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Religious News Service: (4 of 10), 1971-1972 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Religious News Service: (5 of 10), 1973-1974 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Religious News Service: (6 of 10), 1974 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Religious News Service: (7 of 10), 1974-1975 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Religious News Service: (8 of 10), 1975 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Religious News Service: (9 of 10), 1975 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Religious News Service: (10 of 10), 1975 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Religion Today: (1 of 5), 1980 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Religion Today: (2 of 5), 1980 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Religion Today: (3 of 5), 1980 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Religion Today: (4 of 5), 1980 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Religion Today: (5 of 5), 1980-1981 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Religion Today: (1 of 8), 1981 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Religion Today: (2 of 8), 1981 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Religion Today: (3 of 8), 1981 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Religion Today: (4 of 8), 1981 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Religion Today: (5 of 8), 1981 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Religion Today: (6 of 8), 1981 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Religion Today: (7 of 8), 1981 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Religion Today: (8 of 8), 1981 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Religion Today: (1 of 10), 1981 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Religion Today: (2 of 10), 1980-1981 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Religion Today: (3 of 10), 1981 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Religion Today: (4 of 10), 1981 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Religion Today: (5 of 10), 1981 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Religion Today: (6 of 10), 1981 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Religion Today: (7 of 10), 1981 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Religion Today: (8 of 10), 1981 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Religion Today: (9 of 10), 1981 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Religion Today: (10 of 10), 1981 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Religion Today: (1 of 10), 1981-1982 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Religion Today: (2 of 10), 1981-1982 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Religion Today: (3 of 10), 1982 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Religion Today: (4 of 10), 1982 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Religion Today: (5 of 10), 1982 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Religion Today: (6 of 10), 1982 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Religion Today: (7 of 10), 1982 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Religion Today: (8 of 10), 1982 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Religion Today: (9 of 10), 1982 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Religion Today: (10 of 10), 1982 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Response: (1 of 4), 1977-1978 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Response: (2 of 4), 1978 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Response: (3 of 4), 1978 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Response: (4 of 4), 1979 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Response: (1 of 4), 1980-1981 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Response: (2 of 4), 1981-1982 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Response: (3 of 4), 1982 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Response: (4 of 4), 1982 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Response: (1 of 8), 1982-1983 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Response: (2 of 8), 1983 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Response: (3 of 8), 1983 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Response: (4 of 8), 1983-1984 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Response: (5 of 8), 1984 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Response: (6 of 8), 1984 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Response: (7 of 8), 1984 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Response: (8 of 8), 1984 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Response: (1 of 3), 1985 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Response: (2 of 3), 1985-1986 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Response: (3 of 3), 1987 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Response: (1 of 6), 1987-1988 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Response: (2 of 6), 1988-1989 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Response: (3 of 6), 1989-1990 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Response: (4 of 6), 1990-1991 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Response: (5 of 6), 1991-1992 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Response: (6 of 6), 1992-1994 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Richmond Times Dispatch, 1967-1968, 1971 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Seventh Angel: (1 of 10), 1984 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Seventh Angel: (2 of 10), 1984 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Seventh Angel: (3 of 10), 1984 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Seventh Angel: (4 of 10), 1984 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Seventh Angel: (5 of 10), 1984 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Seventh Angel: (6 of 10), 1984 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Seventh Angel: (7 of 10), 1984 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Seventh Angel: (8 of 10), 1984 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Seventh Angel: (9 of 10), 1983-1984 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Seventh Angel: (10 of 10), 1982-1984 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Seventh Angel: (1 of 8), 1984 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Seventh Angel: (2 of 8), 1984 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Seventh Angel: (3 of 8), 1984 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Seventh Angel: (4 of 8), 1984-1985 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Seventh Angel: (5 of 8), 1979, 1981, 1984 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Seventh Angel: (6 of 8), 1984-1985 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Seventh Angel: (7 of 8), 1985 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Seventh Angel: (8 of 8), 1984-1985 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Spectrum: (1 of 4), 1970 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Spectrum: (2 of 4), 1969-1970 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Spectrum: (3 of 4), 1970 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Spectrum: (4 of 4), 1970 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - The Tablet: (1 of 2), 1986-1988, 1994-1995 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - The Tablet: (2 of 2), 1995, 1998, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Traxis: (1 of 7), 1981-1983 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Traxis: (2 of 7), 1980-1981 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Traxis: (3 of 7), 1981 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Traxis: (4 of 7), 1981 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Traxis: (5 of 7), 1981 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Traxis: (6 of 7), 1981 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Traxis: (7 of 7), 1981-1983 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - United Board: (1 of 6), 1967-1969 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - United Board: (2 of 6), 1969-1970, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - United Board: (3 of 6), 1978 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - United Board: (4 of 6), 1989 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - United Board: (5 of 6), 1989 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - United Board: (6 of 6), 1989-1990 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - United Church News, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - United Methodist Communications: (1 of 6), 1978 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - United Methodist Communications: (2 of 6), 1978 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - United Methodist Communications: (3 of 6), 1979 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - United Methodist Communications: (4 of 6), 1981 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - United Methodist Communications: (5 of 6), 1982 (Box 76, Folder 12)